CLAUDIU CREANGA

London, UK | 07860 136073 | claudiu.creanga.backup@gmail.com

ABOUT ME

The best way to know me is to visit my website www.claudiucreanga.me

I started as a frontend developer and used SASS and LESS, Foundation and Bootstrap.

I know **JavaScript** and jQuery. Lately I worked a lot with **PHP (OOP Magento** style). I have a good understanding of magento, backend to frontend, including the dashboard.

In my free time I like to code in **Python** and experiment with angular and node.

I'm good at SEO and Google Analytics.

I learn a new technology very fast and have a passion for coding. Hey, if it is something that I like I often spend my weekend playing with it.

Once I brought pancakes to the office and made everyone happy.

EXPERIENCE

October 2014 - present

Magento developer, Limesharp

- Develop custom themes for Magento using HTML, SASS, PHP, JavaScript, Foundation Framework and Git.
- · SEO improvements for big and heavy traffic websites.
- · Magento catalog management.

March 2014 -October 2014

Frontend Developer, European Commission

- · Lead the Commissioner's Dacian Ciolos IT presence and campaigns.
- · Frontend and backend development for EC's websites.

February 2013 -March 2014

Frontend developer, OSF Global Services

- · Frontend development for ecommerce websites.
- · Responsive web design.

EDUCATION

2013	Masters in Philosophy (History and Philosophy of Science and Technology), University of
	Bucharest

2011 Bachelor's degree in Philosophy, *University of Bucharest*